https://brandablenames.com/privacy-policy/

818-813-4142
Contact Us
FashionScents.comEdibles.usLaughingBadger.comKarmaAngel.comWellnessCon.comBeautifulFaces.comILoveYou.xyzBagOfCandy.comMightyVeggie.comAutoBy.ComPetSittingService.comSaversville.comBoxxco.comBelieveICan.comHaHa.meWiredPineapple.comOnYourWrist.com168Hours.comHeavenlySnacks.comMisterCanna.comFixMeUps.comRocknRolln.comShredALot.comHugables.comRedVases.comUnOpened.netVippio.comReelMusic.comMakeBelieveVille.comLoveYou.meeAutoLoans.comCreditCardz.netSavageCapital.comContentGenie.comBeautifulLips.comWordsOnWings.comMalibu.mobiCheedos.comHigherPleasures.comSmileExperts.comMochaLounge.comGrapeNeon.comFlamingPeppers.comMedBands.comZapso.comAngelsFromHeaven.comMutualConsent.com
Toggle navigation
Home
Categories
About UsPurchasing ProcessBrandable Name FAQs
Keyword(s)
Search Advanced Search
Your cart is empty.
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
At BrandableNames.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy.
We use the information we collect to assist in processing orders. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
The Information We Collect:
BrandableNames.com collects from you the necessary information, such as name, email address and credit card information, to process your order.
We Do Not Share Your Personal Information:
BrandableNames.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. This information is for our private records only. We restrict access of your orders to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Personal information is not available to any third party via our website or through other means.
Spam Email and Use of Email Addresses:
We make every effort to minimize the amount of email correspondence you receive from us. We do not share or sell your email address to any third parties.
Site Security:
We employ the latest 128-bit SSL (Secure Socket Layering) encryption technology in our online shopping cart system. This is done to protect you from unauthorized use of the information you are sending to our server. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser download and install the latest version of your favorite browser, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Safari, Google Chrome, Netscape Communicator or Mozilla Firefox.
Use of Cookies:
BrandableNames.com uses cookies to enhance your shopping and browsing experience and keep track of your order information. The cookies we use DO NOT store any personal information such as your e-mail address, street address, phone number or credit card number.
Security Policy:
To ensure your safety and confidentiality in the shopping cart, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology: the industry standard for transferring sensitive information over the Internet. Our secure server software encrypts (scrambles) all of your personal information including credit card number, name and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
The encryption process takes the characters you enter and converts them into bits of code that are securely transmitted over the Internet and can only be reassembled and read by the owner of the secured site.
Categories
3 to 5 CharactersAdultAutomotiveBabyBrandableBusinessCannabis CBD MarijuanaCryptoDatingDomainEntertainmentFinanceFood BeverageGeographicalHealth BeautyHomeInspirationalInternetLegalLifestyleMarijuanaMedicalMiscellaneousPersonal NamePetProductProfessional ServicesReal EstateServiceShopSloganSportsTravelWearable Technology
